Home is where the heart is
A Christmas Reunion is a comedy, tv movie, family film directed by Sean Olson.
A Madison Avenue executive, Amy, discovers an unusual Christmas
surprise when she inherits her Aunt’s hometown bakery.
The real surprise comes when she learns the other half of the
bakery was left to her long-ago boyfriend, Jack.
Unresolved personal issues resurface between them, as the exes return home to
co-manage the store, along with its traditional holiday cookie bake-off.
Amy Stone, played by Denise Richards.
Jack Evans, played by Patrick Muldoon.
Dylan Carruthers, played by Jake Busey.
Aunt Linda, played by Catherine Hicks.
Don Dupree, played by Parker Stevenson.
Young Jack Evans, played by Brody Fitzgerald.
A Madea Christmas is a 2013 American Christmas comedy film directed, written, produced by and starring Tyler Perry with the rest of the cast consisting of
Kathy Najimy, Chad Michael Murray, Anna Maria Horsford, Tika Sumpter, Eric Lively, JR Lemon, Alicia Witt, Lisa Whelchel, and Larry the Cable Guy.
This is the first Christmas-themed film from the writer-director as it tells the story of Madea going to the fictional town of Bucktussle, Alabama, with her
great-niece to spend Christmas with the great-niece's daughter as financial trouble involving a newly-constructed dam that threatens the town.
This is the seventeenth film by Perry, and the
eighth film in the Madea film series.
The film was released on December 13, 2013, by Lionsgate.
A Madea Christmas received negative reviews from
critics and grossed $53.4 million worldwide.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.